awesomelibrary.org 2015-05-12

# Privacy Policy

Here: [Home](http://www.awesomelibrary.org/) > Privacy **Privacy Policy**

> > ### Privacy Policy
>> 
>> **The Awesome Library does not collect information on visitors to its Website. This is, perhaps, all a visitor or parent needs to know since it covers everything.** To fulfill federal legislative requirements, we are making additional specific statements below.
>> 
>> ### Privacy Policy Regarding Children
>> 
>> **The Awesome Library does not:**
>> 
>> Collect online contact information from a child under 13.   If Awesome Library ever does collect such information, it will gain prior verifiable parental consent or direct parental notification of the nature and intended use of this information, which shall include an opportunity for the parent to prevent use of the information and participation in the activity.   Where prior parental consent is not obtained,online contact information shall only be used to directly respond to the child's request and shall not be used to re-contact the child for other purposes (by [testsforge solution](http://www.testsforge.com/) [pulido](http://www.testsforge.com/expert/daniel_pulido.html)). Emails from children are not saved after responding to their questions.
>> 
>> **The Awesome Library does not:**
>> 
>> Collect personally identifiable offline contact information from children under 13 without prior verifiable parental consent.
>> 
>> **The Awesome Library does not:**
>> 
>> Distribute to third parties any Personally Identifiable Information collected from a child under 13 without prior verifiable parental consent.
>> 
>> Give the ability to children under 13 to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior verifiable parental consent, and will make best efforts to prohibit a child from posting any contact information.
>> 
>> Entice a child under 13 by the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity, to divulge more information than is needed to participate in such activity. 
>> 
>> If the Aweseome Library ever requests personally identifiable information, we will also place prominent notice where personally identifiable information is collected, requesting the child to ask a parent for permission to answer the questions.
>> 
>> ### Privacy Policy Regarding Adults
>> 
>> **The Awesome Library does not:**
>> 
>> Collect personally identifible information.   If it does begin collecting such information, prior consent will be obtained from the users of the site, options will be provided to not provide such information, and the uses of the information will be specified.   If information will be divulged to third parties, users will be notified prior to collecting the information. 

**Back to Top**   
|  | [**Search**](http://www.awesomelibrary.org/help.html):    [**Spelling**](http://www.m-w.com/dictionary.htm)  **Hot Topics** - [**American Flag**](http://www.awesomelibrary.org/Flag.html), [Current Events](http://www.awesomelibrary.org/Classroom/Social_Studies/Current_Events/Current_Events.html), [ Politics](http://www.awesomelibrary.org/Classroom/Social_Studies/Current_Events/Politics.html), [ Education](http://www.awesomelibrary.org/Classroom/Social_Studies/Current_Events/Education.html), [ Environment](http://www.awesomelibrary.org/Classroom/Science/Ecology/Ecology.html), [ Iraq](http://www.awesomelibrary.org/Library/Local_Information/Middle_East/Iraq.html),   [ Biographies](http://www.awesomelibrary.org/Classroom/Social_Studies/History/Biographies.html), [ Multicultural](http://www.awesomelibrary.org/Classroom/Social_Studies/Multicultural/Multicultural.html), [ Encyclopedias](http://www.awesomelibrary.org/Library/Reference_and_Periodicals/General_Reference/Encyclopedias.html), [Medical Care](http://www.awesomelibrary.org/Library/Reference_and_Periodicals/Medical/Medical.html), [Obesity](http://www.awesomelibrary.org/Library/Reference_and_Periodicals/Medical/Obesity.html), [Fitness](http://www.awesomelibrary.org/Classroom/Health_PE/Sports/Fitness.html), [Sports](http://www.awesomelibrary.org/Classroom/Health_PE/Sports/Sports.html), [Holidays](http://www.awesomelibrary.org/Classroom/Social_Studies/Holidays/Holidays.html),   [ Middle East Conflict](http://www.awesomelibrary.org/Classroom/Social_Studies/Current_Events/Middle_East.html), [Terrorism](http://www.awesomelibrary.org/Classroom/Social_Studies/Terrorism/Terrorism.html), [Bullying](http://www.awesomelibrary.org/Office/Counselor/Conflict_Prevention_and_Mediation/Bullying.html), [ Child Heroes](http://www.awesomelibrary.org/Classroom/Social_Studies/World_Peace/Heroes_and_Heroism/Child_Heroes.html), [ World Peace](http://www.awesomelibrary.org/Classroom/Social_Studies/World_Peace/World_Peace.html), [ Election Reform](http://www.awesomelibrary.org/Classroom/Social_Studies/Government/Election_Reform.html),   [**Awesome Talking Library**](http://www.awesomelibrary.org/Awesome_Talking_Library.html), [Spanish](http://www.awesomelibrary.org/espanol.html), [French](http://www.awesomelibrary.org/francais.html), [Italian](http://www.awesomelibrary.org/italiano.html), [German](http://www.awesomelibrary.org/lib-deutsch.html), [**Search the Web**](http://www.awesomelibrary.org/searche.html),    
---|---  
  
Try [Index](http://www.awesomelibrary.org/ind.html), [ New](http://www.awesomelibrary.org/Office/Main/New_and_Exciting/New_and_Exciting.html), [Search Engines](http://www.awesomelibrary.org/searche.html), [Dictionary](http://www.m-w.com/dictionary.htm), or the [Bookstore](http://www.awesomelibrary.org/books.html), [Licenses](http://www.awesomelibrary.org/licenses.html),  
Email Us, [About Us](http://www.awesomelibrary.org/about.html), [Link to Us](http://www.awesomelibrary.org/codes-directories.html), or [Privacy Policy](http://www.awesomelibrary.org/privacy.html).

© 2013 EDI and Dr. R. Jerry Adams
